info desk stoicism knives philosophical system weekend ivied it and trills
问讯处斯多葛主义刀哲学体系周末使它不适和琐事。
essex logic and physics sometimes coolers arrange the suspect of
essex逻辑和物理有时会用冷却器安排
story cm in the form or own the jew now percent the physics do white
故事厘米的形式或现在拥有犹太人的百分比，物理学将白
the fx and the shell the logic according to the scores physics sets the core of
fx和shell根据分数物理的逻辑设置了核心
stoicism deep as we would knowledge about you were kings of the universe
我们深知你是宇宙之王，所以坚忍不拔
fx account of difficult to the chairmen in comparison to the fluidity of sx de
外汇比起sx de的流动性而言，主席的困难
solidity of logic fund the shell based on the story he wants percent
逻辑的坚固性基于他想要的故事为壳提供了资金
you the three pillars of stoicism [Music]
您是坚忍主义的三大支柱[音乐]
before ajax square something aspect or piece of philosophy starring with the shell and and
在Ajax Square之前，以贝壳为主体的某些方面或哲学作品，以及
urge the duo owen to point out that these aspects of
敦促二人组指出这些方面
inter deep and it and the dewy one or the other de
间深，它和露水一个或另一个德
system which lapse so lets drive in one logic who might
因此，让我们以一种逻辑驱动可能
take a rational thinking about cheese and effect for granted
对奶酪和效果的理性思考是理所当然的
bad in the plague you thinking didn't always work that way and to be honest
在瘟疫中你认为并非总是那样运作是坏事，说实话
there are still many people who are getting that much to come up with a logical argument and
仍然有很多人想出一个合理的论据，
in that charlie led by their emotions logic is an art weiss of my fears
在他们的情感逻辑引导下的查理是我恐惧中的一种艺术
pieces for skills and philosophical de bijt die yogini's one of the surviving
技巧和哲学的碎片约吉尼是幸存者之一
sources for disturbing logic set and a quote
干扰逻辑集和引号的来源
and this is what the stick sorry like and logical meters
这就是棍子抱歉和逻辑米的含义
so they can maintain that and wiseman is oliseh die lactation
这样他们就可以保持和明智的人泌乳不育
for everything is a trick consideration of white
一切都是白色的绝妙考虑
in argument over what belongs to the topic of physics and recognizing was belongs
关于属于物理学主题的东西的争论，并且认识到属于
to fx and quote who coach side logic is not only the hard shell that holes and
FX并引述谁指导主教练的逻辑不仅仅是硬洞
tricks and physics together with if we the fans will be pie or reasoning
技巧和物理学，以及我们的粉丝是否愿意做出决定或推理
that must be master in order to engage in the other two aspects of piece
必须精通才能参与作品的其他两个方面
philosophy thrusts logic is based on language snail
哲学推论逻辑基于语言蜗牛
propositions the rider stands out well and I sample if you watching this video
建议骑手脱颖而出，如果您观看此视频，我会抽样说明
sure look out of the window most likely kids light outsite that you
一定要看着窗外，最有可能的是孩子们在外面照亮了你
can make the following proposition ede is light and fits in the daytime des
可以使下面的命题轻而易举，适合白天的设计
propositions two things in the middle of the night
提议在半夜里有两件事
this proposition is falls to explain this week and a bit more complex
这个命题是本周要解释的事情，要复杂一些
itude argument and make the following proposition
经度论点，并提出以下命题
fsd in is light according to this takes the system of losing is what I'm talking about
fsd in轻按此采取丢失的系统是我在说的
a char universe i have all these logos and stewart logic which
一个char宇宙，我拥有所有这些徽标和斯图尔特逻辑，
is widely used all round at the time I was walking the principles of existence
在我漫步生存原则的时候被广泛使用
2 fx Tried some extra and some actor wet tries les jours the woman in them
2 fx尝试了一些额外的动作和一些演员湿试les玩弄了其中的女人
for this one to keep it a bit organize stokes argue that once
为了使这一点保持组织性，斯托克斯认为，一旦
ef master de arteries en week and the german osx
每周的EF Master de Arteries和德国的osx
lady sting west virtue what you already is, continue to happiness and vice what you
斯汀·西德夫人，你已经是什么，继续幸福，反之，你是什么
everything contribution to misery the punch subdivided virtue and to
对苦难的一切贡献使美德得以细分
for classifications moderation justice scratch and with dan
用于分类适度公正的划痕，并与丹
in the same way they saw previder 5st your in justice howard is in
他们以同样的方式看待《正义前传5st》，霍华德（Howard）在
temperance and foolishness with whom and vice and virtualizer you great
节制和愚蠢的人，与谁和恶习和虚拟化的人，你很棒
area of ​​things i do not necessarily bed necessary i could this class escort in
东西的区域我不一定需要睡觉，我可以在这节课中护送
de france at the steaks whether or not you this playmobil azure
在牛排上享受法国美食，无论您是否喜欢这种天蓝色
by engaging in that sense the pen differs to the context and get your ability
通过从事这种意义上的笔不同的上下文，并获得您的能力
to whom she helps you the site how to act in other words in the air france aren't
她向您提供帮助的网站不是如何在空中行动的
necessarily harmful of contra beauty to happiness is the pants on the way you
反对美对幸福必定有害的是你前进道路上的裤子
use them so you keep used and according to see if
使用它们，以便您继续使用并根据是否
city ​​and founder or the stoic school of redemption is the goal of life to see
城市和创始人或救赎的坚守学校是人生的目标
moovly flow too long with the natural course i stayed it and i become or excel
顺着自然路线流淌的时间太长了，我留下来了，变得或脱颖而出
powerpoint single system which is colton nature
Powerpoint单一系统，属于科尔顿性质
that individual life is good we it is in harmony with nature and quote of
个人生活是美好的，我们与自然和谐相处，
course virtue is a perfect agreement with nature who chose vice and knows nature
当然，美德是与自然的完美协议，选择恶习并了解自然
of the bowl of soup in difference the fault distinguished preferred in the
一碗汤的区别在于故障在
france and this preferred indifference i samples of preferred in de france there
法国和这个偏爱的人在法国偏爱的样本
soon pleasure and good reputation the attributes of positive in regards to
很快的愉悦和良好的声誉
all natural condition but don't necessarily two happiness examples of
都是自然状态，但不一定有两个幸福的例子
this free for difference of disease witness bobines poverty and loan
这种无疾而终的见证人使贫穷和借贷成为现实
repetition the attributes to negative and
将属性重复为负数和
recordstore and hecho con dish and that it don't necessarily then misery
唱片店和hecho con菜，并不一定那么痛苦
agent2 those are the futsal use the terms of the lead to a happy life or not
agent2这些是五人制足球是否会使用导致幸福生活的条件
he had to and with a thousand more to sex with in story season but the sorrow the
在故事季中，他不得不与一千多人发生性关系，但悲哀的是
basics 3 physics live according to nature
基础知识3物理学根据自然而生
we came to understanding of nature the story can be set
我们开始了解自然可以设定故事
of physics and as well be takes nature because we can agree compared to another
是自然的，因为我们可以同意与另一种相比
matter physics and short stay the physics
物质物理学和短期物理学
or simply their understanding of the universe like sx
或者仅仅是他们对宇宙的理解，如sx
physics is a fixed system of ideas and concepts
物理学是思想和观念的固定系统
like any bolts basiqs the steam in a bun like something and that he
像任何螺栓一样，将蒸汽包裹在小圆面包中，就像他
takes logos which was already a campus in for some
带有一些已经在校园里的徽标
reason in their views existence is based on
他们认为存在的原因是基于
major and number with there is wifi or sensus knows exactly what is base and
专业和编号与wifi或sensus确切知道什么是基础，
lifeless of it self and so is the power cable
它本身没有生命，电源线也没有生命
direct force behind the ever-changing manifestation of the cosmos is what the
宇宙不断变化的表现背后的直接力量是
stowbox colt hats now complete beaming draw or the break from major and cannot
Stowbox Colt帽子现在完成了喜洋洋的抽奖或与Major的突破，无法
be destroyed the famous stone gray cypers descried numa is the four kool of vlogs
被毁的著名的石灰色cycys描述努玛是四个博客的博客
dat structures meter simply put numa makes the universe live the movement of
dat结构测量仪简单地将numa置于使宇宙活着的运动中
stars and planets sexist of life the orphan or see
恒星和行星性别歧视生活的孤儿还是看
already determined at nima and is based on in rational principle of logos
已由尼玛（Nima）确定，并基于徽标的合理原则
the studs polite and direction is already the german
饰钉的礼貌和方向已经是德国人
however they also viewed peter countless other realistic
但是他们也看到了彼得无数其他现实的事物
the planning includes choice is mimicry and so many different patch to follow the
该计划包括模仿，因此要遵循许多不同的补丁
soft determinism is very similar to Islam known Kristin views
软决定论与伊斯兰已知的克里斯汀观点非常相似
on the wall ar destiny's already written in the stars and on the other hand you
在墙上，命运已经写在星星上，另一方面，
still have free want it is a too subscribet stones is a high-profile
仍然有免费的需求，这是一个太订阅的石头，是备受瞩目的
impact and christianity and so loved combinations with Islam is already the case
影响力和基督教，因此与伊斯兰教的热爱结合已经成为事实
douwes him and buddhism arthur special smarter spectators him
douwes他和佛教亚瑟特别聪明的观众他
in several ways that's it thank you for watching
从几个方面来说都是这样，谢谢您的观看
the music]
音乐]
[Music]
[音乐]